Preliminary Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art archives department records, circa 1890-2007 COR0005.3.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Audiovisual and graphics records, circa 1869-2014; 1950-1984; Series 1; 24 Linear Feet
  - Photographs, circa 1890-1984; Series 1 Subseries 1; 37.5 Linear Feet Over 1,353 images
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; American Images, Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 27)
      P1981.0339
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; 36th Biennial Opening, 23 February 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 28)
      P1981.0342
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Photographs from the Collection of Sam Wagstaff, 3 February 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; 5 prints (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 29)
      P1981.0343
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; W. Clark Collection Opening, 25 April 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 30)
      P1981.0345
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; 11 Southern Photographers Opening, 24 August 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; print, 2 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 31)
      P1981.0346
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Manuel Alvarez Bravo, 29 September 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 32)
      P1981.0347
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Daumier in Retrospect (Dinner), 19 September 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 33)
      P1981.0348
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Alma Thomas Opening, 8 September 1972; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 34)
      P1981.0350
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Irish Imagination Opening, 20 October 1972; Series 1 subseries 1; prints (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 35)
      P1981.0352
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Manuel Alvarez Bravo, 29 September 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; 5 prints (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 36)
      P1981.0536
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Sally Drummond Opening, 2 November 1972; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 37)
      P1981.0970
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Irish Imagination Opening, 20 October 1972; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints; 4 prints (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folders 38-39)
      P1981.0971A-B
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Shalom of Safed Opening, 15 November 1972; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 40)
      P1981.0972
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Ed McGowins: True Stories Opening, 12 September 1975; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 41)
      P1981.0821
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; M.J. Gross Collection of Edward Potthast Opening, 15 March 1973; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 negative strips (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 42)
      P1981.0989
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; J.J. Akston Opening, 4 May 1972; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 43)
      P1981.0990
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Turker Ozoogan Opening, 7 September 1972; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 44)
      P1981.0992
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Joseph P. White Opening, 15 September 1972; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 45)
      P1981.0995
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Art of Franklin County Jail, 15 September 1972; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints, contact sheet (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 46)
      P1981.0996
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Photographs from the Collection of Sam Wagstaff, 3 February 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 47)
      P1981.1061
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Bierstadt Retrospective, 7 April 1972; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 48)
      P1983.0090
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Member's Opening, 1974-1975; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 49)
      P1983.0139
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; H. Marc Mayens Coll, 12 December 1969; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folder 50)
      P1984.0135
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Norman Rockwell Retrospective, 26 May 1972; Series 1 subseries 1; 5 prints; 4 prints (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folders 51-52)
      P1984.0161
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Soviet Union: Arts and Crafts in Ancient Times and Today, 14 January 1972; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints (Box 5, Flat box 24, Folders 53-54)
      P1984.0162
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Treasures of Ancient Nigeria Opening, 17 December 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 6 prints, color print (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 1)
      P1981.0005
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Georges Van Tangerloo Opening, 21 April 1980; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 2)
      P1981.0006
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Jerome Liebling Opening, 5 December 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 3)
      P1981.0025A
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Personal Narratives: Brunner and Ryan, 5 December 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints; print (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folders 4-5)
      P1981.0025B-C
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Images of the 70's Opening, 18 January 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints; print; 6 prints; 4 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folders 6-9)
      P1981.0042A-D
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Armand Hammer Collection, 1 October 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 10)
      P1981.0046
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; John Alexander Opening, 29 March 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints; 2 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folders 11-12)
      P1981.0057A-B
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Helen Levitt: Photography Opening, 9 February 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints; 2 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folders 13-14)
      P1981.0060A-B
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Contemporary Art of Senegal Opening, 22 February 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 15)
      P1981.0061
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Puppets: Art and Entertainment Opening, 6 June 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 16)
      P1981.0070
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Contemporary Art of Senegal Opening, 22 February 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 17)
      P1981.0079
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Treasures of Ancient Nigeria Opening, 17 December 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 5 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 18)
      P1981.0081
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Vija Celmis/Frank Gillette Opening, 18 September 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 contact sheets; 2 prints (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folders 19-20)
      P1981.0084A-B
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Personal Narratives: Brunner and Ryan, 4 December 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints, contact sheet (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 21)
      P1981.0086
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Jerome Liebling Opening, 5 December 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 22)
      P1981.0088
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Guy Pene du Bois Opening, 10 October 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 23)
      P1981.0089
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Vija Celmis/Frank Gillette Opening, 18 September 1980; Subseries 1.1; 3 prints; 2 contact sheets; 3 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folders 24-26)
      P1981.0092A-C
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Armand Hammer Collection, 1 October 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 contact sheets; 9 prints (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folders 27-28)
      P1981.0094A-B
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Armand Hammer Collection, 1 October 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 contact sheets; 5 prints (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folders 29-30)
      P1981.0095A-B
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Armand Hammer Collection, 1 October 1980; Series 1 subseries; 3 prints (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 31)
      P1981.0096
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Armand Hammer Collection, 1 October 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 32)
      P1981.0098
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Treasures of Ancient Nigeria Opening, 17 December 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet; 6 negative strips (C missing) (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folders 33-34)
      P1981.0100A-C
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Contemporary Art of Senegal Opening, 22 February 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 35)
      P1981.0340
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Mayo/Dickson Opening, 22 May 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 36)
      P1981.0355
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Helen Levitt: Photography Opening, 8 February 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 37)
      P1981.0338
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Images of the 70's Opeing, 18 January 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 6 prints (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 38)
      P1981.0341
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Guy Pene du Bois Exhibition Opening, 10 October 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 6 prints (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 39)
      P1982.0003
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Hammer Masterpiece Dinner, 1 October 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 7 prints (Box 5, Flat box 25, Folder 40)
      P1984.0075
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Billy Al Bengston Dinner, 30 January 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 1)
      P1981.0008, P1981.0077A-B
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; P.H. Polk Opening, 18 February 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 contact sheets; negative (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folders 2-3)
      P1981.29A-B
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Adolph Gottlieb Opening, 28 April 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints; 5 negatives; contact sheet (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folders 4-6)
      P1981.0064A-D
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Peter Thomas, 13 May 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet, 3 negatives (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folders 7-8)
      P1981.0065A-B
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Collage on Paper, 8 May 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints; contact sheet; 5 negatives (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folders 9-11)
      P1981.0066A-C
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; P.H. Polk Opening, 18 February 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 12)
      P1981.0076A
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Billy Al Bengston Dinner, 30 January 1981; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folders 13-14)
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Da Vinci-Codex Leicesters, 17 January 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints; 8 prints; 8 prints; 11 prints (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folders 15-18)
      P1981.0099A-D
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; 37th Biennial Opening, 18 February 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 19)
      P1981.0353
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Frank Wright Opening, 12 June 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints, 2 contact sheets; 5 negatives (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folders 20-21)
      P1981.1071A-B
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Closing Ceremonies of Contemporary Art of Senegal, 6 April 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 22)
      P1982.0002
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; James Peale Polk Opening, 17 July 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 contact sheets, print, negative (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 23)
      P1983.0002
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Spanish Art Tomorrow reception given for the King and Queen of Spain, 14 October 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; 8 contact sheets, print; 7 prints, negative; 4 prints (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folders 24-26)
      P1983.0005A-C
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Of Time and Place, 21 September 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints; 2 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folders 27-28)
      P1983.0006A-B
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Mark Cohen and Narrative Wood, 9 October 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints, contact sheet (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 29)
      P1983.0007
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Black Folk Art Mrs. Reagan's Visit, Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 30)
      P1983.0012
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Charles Pratt Exhibition Opening, 13 May 1982; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet, negative (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 31)
      P1983.0014
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Northern Lights Press Preview with Kirk Varnedoe, 10 September 1982; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet, negatives (Box 5, Flat box 36, Folder 32)
      P1983.0016
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Linda Connor and Acquisitions since 1975, 19 November 1982; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet, negatives (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 33)
      P1983.0025
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Video Area Show Press Preview, 15 September 1982; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet, negatives (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 34)
      P1983.0024
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Recollections Opening Day, 26 November 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet, negative (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 35)
      P1983.0036
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Washington on the Potomac and Washington Photography, 19 February 1982; Series 1 subseries 1; 5 prints (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 36)
      P1983.0084
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Bob Timberlake Dinner, 1 August 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 37)
      P1983.0086
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Bob Timberlake Dinner, 1 August 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints; 5 prints (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folders 38-39)
      P1983.0087A-B
    - Special events -- Exhibition opening; August Sanders Preview, 1982 December 17; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 40)
      1983.0098
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Wright Morris Press Preview/Reception, 15 March 1983; Series 1 subseries 1; print; 5 contact sheets; 2 prints (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folders 41-43)
      P1983.0218A-C
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; 38th Biennial Philip Morris Opening, 1 February 1983; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints, 2 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 44)
      P1983.0220
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; 38th Biennial Press Conference, 2 February 1983; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints, contact sheet (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 45)
      P1983.0221
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; 38th Biennial Members Opening, 2 February 1983; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints, 3 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 46)
      P1983.0222
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Neil Jenney Dinner, 11 September 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; 5 contact sheets (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folder 47)
      P1984.0074
    - Special Events -- Exhibit openings; Mrs. Reagan's visit to greet artists viewing Black Folk Art, January 1982; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints; 4 prints (Box 5, Flat box 26, Folders 48-49)
      P1984.0142A-B
    - Special Events -- Lectures; Yehudi Menuhi, 17 March 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 5 prints. 2 contact sheets (Box 6, Flat box 27, Folder 1)
      P1981.0028
    - Special Events -- Lectures; P.H. Polk (Gallery Talk), 8 April 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 27, Folder 2)
      P1981.0076B
    - Special Events -- Lectures; Bill Christenberry, 10 September 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print; 2 prints (Box 6, Flat box 27, Folders 3-4)
      P1981.0091A-B
    - Special Events -- Lectures; "Photography: Where We Are", 25 February 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; 5 prints; 5 prints (Box 6, Flat box 27, Folders 5-6)
      P1981.0193A-B
    - Special Events -- Lectures; Barbara Tuchman Lecture, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints (Box 6, Flat box 27, Folder 7)
      P1981.0194
    - Special Events -- Lectures; Free Admission Dedication, 19 April 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 contact sheets; 7 prints (Box 6, Flat box 27, Folders 8-9)
      P1981.0195A-B
    - Special Events -- Lectures; 3rd Film Festival for Children, 24 July 1964; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 6, Flat box 27, Folder 10)
      P1981.0281
    - Special Events -- Lectures; Andy Warhol Booksigning, December 1975; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints; contact sheet, print (Box 6, Flat box 27, Folders 11-12)
      P1981.0349A-B
    - Special Events -- Lectures; Sotheby Parke Bernet Auction of 19th C. European Ptgs. from the Corcoran, 3 May 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; 5 prints; 4 prints; (C missing); 4 prints; 4 prints (Box 6, Flat box 27, Folders 13-17)
      P1981.0404A-E
    - Special Events -- Lectures; Harry Callahan, 23 September 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 6, Flat box 27, Folder 18)
      P1981.1069
    - Special Events -- Lectures; Barryman Ridges Lectures on Baron E. Von Maydell, 9 November 1951; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 6, Flat box 27, Folder 19)
      P1981.1242B
    - Special Events -- Lectures; The Artist in American History, 27 October 1950; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 27, Folder 20)
      P1981.1245B
    - Special Events -- Lectures; Isaac Stern at Washington Art Group, 17 November 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints (Box 6, Flat box 27, Folders 21-22)
      P1983.0042A-B
    - Special Events -- Lectures; Photography Symposium, 25 February 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; 5 prints; 6 prints; 6 prints; 4 prints (Box 6, Flat box 27, Folders 23-26)
      P1983.0172A-D
    - Special Events -- Lectures; Washington Art Group Luncheon Meeting, 10 November 1975; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 27, Folder 27)
      P1984.0076
    - Special Events -- Lectures; Lord Clark Lecture, 4 April 1971; Series 1 subseries 1; print, 4 contact sheets; 4 contact sheets (Box 6, Flat box 27, Folders 28-29)
      P1984.0129A-B
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; National Symphony String Quartet, 31 December 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 6 prints (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 1)
      P1981.0036
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; The Contemporary Music Forum, 1979-1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 2)
      P1981.0101
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; National Symphony String Quartet, 1976-1977; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 3)
      P1981.0105
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Paul Badura-Kaoda Concert, 1959; Series 1 subseries 1; print; 2 negatives (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folders 4-5)
      P1981.0138A-B
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Stars and Bars Band, 25 August 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 6)
      P1981.0184
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Osian Ellis, Harpist, 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 7)
      P1981.0185
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Tokyo String Quartet, 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 8)
      P1981.0186
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Ronald Thomas, Cellist, 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 9)
      P1981.0187
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; National Symphony String Quartet, 1976-1977; Series 1 subseries 1; negatives (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 10)
      P1981.0277
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; David Amram Concert, October 1967; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 negatives (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 11)
      P1981.0278
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Gita Karasick, Pianist, 2 March 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 12)
      P1981.0818
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Paul Badura-Kaoda Concert, 1959; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 13)
      P1981.0967
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Rostropovitch and Mrs. Wyant Vanderpool, November 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 14)
      P1983.0008
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Tokyo String Quartet, 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 15)
      P1983.0009
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Evening with Joshua Logan, August 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 16)
      P1983.0010
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Tokyo String Quartet with Slade and Kreeger, circa 1970-1975; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 17)
      P1983.0138
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Helen Katz Concert, 1977-1978; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 18)
      P1984.0051
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Chilingiran String Quartet, 1977-1978; Series 1 subseries 1; 7 prints (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 19)
      P1984.0053
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Mark K. Clinton, 1975-1976; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 20)
      P1984.0054
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Mount Union Bass Choir, 1974-1975; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 21)
      P1984.0055
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Tokyo String Quartet, 1976-1977; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 22)
      P1984.0056
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Tokyo String Quartet, 1977-1978; Series 1 subseries 1; 11 prints (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 23)
      P1984.0057
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Tokyo String Quartet, 1978-1979; Series 1 subseries 1; 12 prints (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 24)
      P1984.0058
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Alan and Nancy Mondel, 25 April 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 25)
      P1984.0059
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; The American String Quartet, 1978-1979; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 26)
      P1984.0060
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Stephanie Brown Youth Concert, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints, negative (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 27)
      P1984.0061
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Helen Unsula Katz, 30 October 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 28)
      P1984.0062
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Jacquelyn Helin Concert, 1981-1982; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 29)
      P1984.0063
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Osian Ellis, Harp Concert, 1977-1978; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 30)
      P1984.0064
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Carla Hubner, 1977-1978; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 31)
      P1984.0065
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Annapolis Brass Quintet, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 32)
      P1984.0066
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Ingrid and Robert McDonald, 5 November 1976; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 33)
      P1984.0067
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Robert and Arlene Portney, 19 November 1976; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 34)
      P1984.0068
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Cleveland String Quartet, 1981-1982; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints, contact sheet (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 35)
      P1984.0072
    - Special Events -- Musical Events; Cello Performance by Charlotte Moorman, 24 July 1969; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints (Box 6, Flat box 28, Folder 36)
      P1984.0164